<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Philosophical Anatomy</title>
    <link>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Philosophical Anatomy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 20:50:01 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://thephilotomy.ml/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Let It All Go!</title>
      <link>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/justletitallgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 20:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/justletitallgo/</guid>
      <description>Most of us have watched the movie Zindagi Na Milegi Dobara. The movie was a gold mine for philosophy if you ask me. It gave strong insights of what life can be when you let go and face your fears. One of the scenes that really hit me was when the three friends decide to go sky diving. I still remember the part when Arjun turns to his rather nervous friend Imraan, and tells him to &amp;ldquo;just let it all go&amp;rdquo; (signaling him to jump off the plane and face his fear).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-worth...?</title>
      <link>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/selfworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 14:04:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/selfworth/</guid>
      <description>Don’t we all like getting the Royal treatment?
YES!
We all initially start out as loving ourselves and slowly that’s what we forget to do the most. We start allowing others to define what our value is and soon enough we perceive that as the truth of who we really are. Many a times it happens because we give too much of an importance to other people and not enough to ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rising Up And Falling</title>
      <link>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/risingupandfalling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 14:04:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/risingupandfalling/</guid>
      <description>Life is a roller coaster. It has its twists and turns. Its heights and its depths. We all eventually take a fall at least once in our life. A great amount of our time is taken away in building an empire for ourselves. We let our passion take control of us. We put in great hard work, determination, efforts and time into full filling dreams. The office table transforms into a bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Not So Negative Approach</title>
      <link>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/notsonegative/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 13:21:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/notsonegative/</guid>
      <description>Life can be a hassle at times. It has its ups and downs, pros and cons etc&amp;hellip; But many a times we fail to see the true essence of what life really is. Too frequently we give ourselves to the devastating things that happen around us. We let our demons control what and who we really are. We hold ourselves a slave to our assumptions and conclusions. And in the end&amp;hellip;what do we get out of it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grudge Theory</title>
      <link>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/thegrudgetheory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 14:04:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thephilotomy.ml/post/thegrudgetheory/</guid>
      <description>How many times in life do we meet someone who we end up strongly disliking? Happens quite often. We end up fighting with people and carry that baggage of disgust and hatred with us through out life. Its all part of human nature. These are all basic feelings that we all experience. But have you ever thought of a different approach? Something out of the box and completely different?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>